searchengineworkshops.com 2017-11-19

# Search engine workshops: Our Privacy Policy.

## Search Engine Workshops

> **What personally identifiable information is collected on this site?**   
> Visitors may supply personally identifiable information (such as name, address or telephone numbers) for various purposes on this site. These purposes include registering to receive e-mail newsletters, requesting further information about our workshops or services, or simply asking a question about Search Engine Workshops (SEW). SEW does not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. This means that you can visit our site without telling us who you are or revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. 
> 
> **How is it used?**   
> When you supply information about yourself for a specific purpose, we use the information for only that purpose (such as to provide the service or information you have requested). For example, you may be asked to give us individual information to receive information or register for a workshop. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy that means that we do not intend to sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent. 
> 
> Should any material changes be made to the ways in which we use personally identifiable information, SEW will post the changes to our use of personally identifiable information on our site at least 30 days prior to a change. 
> 
> **Security**   
> Personally identifiable information is stored on our Web server and is not publicly accessible. Further, personally identifiable information is only accessed by SEW employees on a "need to know" basis. SEW uses reasonable precautions to keep the information disclosed to us secure. 
> 
> Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties that receive the information. Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your personal information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 
> 
> **Choice/Opt-out**   
> If you have registered to receive e-mail communications from us and later change your mind, you may contact us to have your name removed from our distribution lists. You have the following options to do this: 
> 
> You can send an email to: [privacy@searchengineworkshops.com](mailto:privacy@searchengineworkshops.com).
> 
> You can send mail to:  
> Search Engine Workshops  
> 66 Harrison Drive  
> Newmarket, Ontario  
> Canada  
> L3Y 4P4
> 
> **Correct/Update**   
> If you would like to verify the data we have received from you or to make corrections to it, you may contact us directly at the e-mail and mail addresses provided above. 
> 
> **What anonymous information is collected on this site?**   
> Anonymous clickstream information is collected for every visitor to this site. This includes pages viewed, date and time, and browser type. IP numbers are not stored, but are temporarily used to determine domain type and in some cases, geographic region. We do not make any association between this information and a visitor's identity. 
> 
> **How is it used?**  
>  We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, but do not collect and evaluate this information for individuals. Our Web servers do not record e-mail addresses of the visitors. 
> 
> **How does this site use cookies?**   
> From time to time, SEW or its advertisers may send a "cookie" to your computer. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Cookies do not damage your system. This information is collected to identify your account with the source of advertising that brought you to the site. 
> 
> You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at some Web sites may be diminished and some features may not work as intended. 
> 
> **Links**
> 
> This site may contain links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours. 
> 
> **E-mail Links**   
> We use e-mail links located on this site to allow you to contact us directly via e-mail. We use the information provided in your e-mail to respond to your questions or comments. We may also store your comments for future reference. Your personal information is only shared with third parties with your explicit permission. 
> 
> **Legal Disclaimer**  
>  We may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on SEW. 
> 
> **Consent to Agreement**  
>  By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of information by SEW as specified above. 
> 
> **For more information**  
>  If you have any questions, concerns or comments, please e-mail [privacy@searchengineworkshops.com](mailto:privacy@searchengineworkshops.com).
> 
> **Search Engine Workshops . . . _the premiere onsite search engine marketing workshops in the world!_**

| 

#### Unlock extraordinary traffic potential!

| 

� 2002-2008 SearchEngineWorkshops.com. All rights reserved. Duplication or reproduction  
of the contents of this web site, including, but not limited to, content, graphics and  
source code, is prohibited without expressed written consent by SearchEngineWorkshops.com.
